I'm interested in the technology
raw mentioned in the raw material
[snorts]
known as a prana vacuum. How can we
create
a
prana vacuum
using today's technology?
The so-called prana vacuum is the same
thing as the idea of what you might call
the quantum vacuum. Is the same thing as
the zero point energy concept that many
people are talking about on your planet.
It exists all around you. The technology
exists that you can use to tap into it
in certain ways. Many of the kinds of
things that people have invented that
say it's tapping into the zero point
energy are not exactly doing so. But the
idea is growing in the consciousness,
the collective consciousness of your
planet until such time as that awareness
evolves into technology that will truly
tap into that prana field, the quantum
field, the void, and whatever else you
may wish to call it. It will allow you
unlimited energy, unlimited flow, and
inexhaustible supply of energy that can
be utilized in a variety of ways once
you truly tap into that technology. It
has to do with creating devices of
proper resonance, proper frequencies,
capacitors that vibrate at certain
resonant frequencies that deliver and
transform energy in a certain way. Step
it down in a way that you can use with
your technology. We have talked a little
bit about this as a space-time antenna
concept. Three nested spheres separated
by fatio diameters penetrated by antenni
that are insulated from a merka, a
double interpenetrated tetrahedrin in
the center of the three spheres that
resonates at certain frequencies and can
be activated by the introduction of
energy into it and it will output energy
of a higher caliber, a higher level and
a higher frequency, tapping into the
quantum field in certain ways. But many
people on your planet, a few of them are
beginning to experiment with this and we
cannot deliver more information about
this device until they have already
achieved what it is we have already
delivered. End of discussion.
>> Hello Bashar.
>> Good day.
>> Uh thank you for having this
conversation with each other in this
way.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure to do
so. What would you like to discuss?
>> Talking about the hybrid children. Um
you've mentioned in the past that
contact between hybrid children and
their mothers will expand over time.
>> Yes.
>> Has this process indeed started on this
timeline? Is there is there an increase
of physical contact between human beings
and the hybrid children?
>> Yes, but in an altered reality, not
necessarily physically on your planet so
much, but in a slightly altered version
of physical reality. And in dream time,
these encounters have increased.
>> Okay. Wonderful.
>> Eventually, it will leak into the
physical reality as you understand it.
>> Although it will still be of a higher
vibration than it is now.
>> Yes. Understand. Yeah. And um I also
wanted to talk to you about suppressed
memories.
>> Yes.
>> During our previous conversation, you've
mentioned that I was visited by the
grace when I also was a child.
>> Yes. And that these experiences are
buried deep within my consciousness.
>> Well, not that deep.
>> Oh, not that deep. [laughter]
You also mentioned that I felt
victimized because my childlike state
was not able to comprehend what was
going on during these visitations.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And is it correct to say that from
the point of view as a human being child
that these visitations and the removal
of genetic material was somehow
experienced as a trauma on a
psychological level?
>> Yes, but only because of the way you
were raised as a human. Not because it's
innate to the being a child. Not because
it's innate to being a human child. just
because of the way your planet views
these kinds of things and because it is
shortsighted in its compartmentalization
of awareness. That's the only reason you
experienced it traumatically.
>> And is that also the reason that we're
still somehow afraid of
extraterrestrials?
>> Because you are afraid of portions of
your own power and the extraterrestrials
you're encountering represent and
reflect the idea of your true power in
certain ways. Uh I understand and that
yeah that's probably not a coincidence
but that leads up to my next question.
Um
both my parents have transitioned almost
within three years of each other and the
last parent my father passed one year
ago.
>> Yes.
>> And their physical absence caused a
shift in my life.
>> Yes. Of course that's the purpose of it.
>> Yeah. Um, I experienced this as a
tremendous opportunity to shed a whole
bunch of negative belief systems that I
have bestowed upon myself through their
upbringing.
>> Well, congratulations. That is a
positive way to use it.
>> Thank you. But I also sense that this
tremendous opportunity is sometimes a
bit frightening.
>> Why?
>> As if this whole new space that has
opened up is sometimes too big to
handle.
>> Impossible. Otherwise, you wouldn't
experience it.
You only grow into the space you're
ready for. So no matter how it looks,
you're making a comparison, still using
some of the outdated beliefs to view it
instead of letting go of those outdated
beliefs and understanding you cannot
experience more than you're ready for
anyway.
You can expand into it. That's why it
looks that big because that's how big
you actually are when you let go of the
limiting beliefs.
>> Mhm. I understand what you're saying.
>> I understand what you're saying.
>> And I also um am aware of the physical
impact of this awareness.
>> Yes.
>> Uh uh for instance, when my body is
sleeping,
>> Yes.
>> it seems to respond to this awareness
with an actual physical shock during the
night that eventually wakes me up.
>> Yes, it can. Because again your body is
not used to the vibration or frequency
of energy but it can get used to it over
time.
>> And how how how can we do that? Can you
say something about um how to to
integrate this new space and the
awareness of new space and the physical
response to this? Is it just going with
the flow, letting it happen? That
>> that's one way practice in a sense
having it happen over and over again.
You'll get used to it. That's one way.
But one way to accelerate that is to
understand or have a perspective
where physical reality isn't really
separate from spirit reality. It's
really not so different. It's just that
you've defined it as very different.
You've placed certain definitions on
physical reality that makes it seem so
unlike spirit reality when in fact it's
a natural extension of it.
>> Okay. and the and the and the and the
physical body that reacts um um how can
we smoothen that out? Well, this is what
I'm telling you. Stop making such a
separation in your belief system between
the idea of your physical body and your
spirit. Your physical body is your
spirit in physical terms. Mhm.
>> It's the same kind of idea, if you wish,
a crude analogy of saying
ice is still water.
It's just frozen,
>> but it's the same thing. It's the same
substance essentially, and so is steam.
So if you start looking at your body as
if it's simply euphemistically a frozen
version of your spirit or at least a
portion of your spirit, you can start to
allow the physical reality to sort of
melt a little bit more,
>> allow it to become a little bit more
fluid, a little bit more liquid and not
be so different from the liquid version
or the steam version. So you have to
start really looking at physical reality
as if it's just another state of being
of spirit and not really separate. It's
the idea of separation that's tripping
you up.
>> Yeah, I understand. Understand.
>> And um
you also said something about um that
the human beings on earth will become
more and more human over time.
Yes. You're actually not fully human
yet.
>> Yeah. And I was wondering what you meant
by that. What does it mean to be human
as opposed to not being fully human?
>> Being fully human means that you
understand that everything is made of
unconditional love. You understand that
everything is connected. Everything is a
reflection of everything else and you
act accordingly.
>> Yes. Being fully human is what you
ascribe to beings like Christ, Buddha,
Krishna, so on and so forth. It's the
idea of the behavior that reflects the
godhood within you.
>> Yes.
Yeah. And that probably also means that
um we're not so compartmentalized in our
way of thinking then.
>> Exactly. You think more holistically,
more as a whole system. That's why I
said you understand everything is one
thing. I am you from another point of
view. Literally, I am you from another
point of view. You are us from another
point of view. A fully realized human
lives
in that truth.
>> Yeah. Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> You are so welcome. Ao.
>> Ao.
Greetings Bashar. I have a question for
you. What is the template level of our
space-time reality? You've mentioned
that there is a template level and that
we are each exploring themes
from this template level that there is a
specific template for our lives. I'm
wondering if this template is actually
revealed in the deck of [snorts] what we
consider 52 playing cards. And if this
template level of reality is expressed,
symbolized in the deck of 52 playing
cards, where exactly did these cards
come from? Who created them and when?
And what is the best way for us to
utilize these cards now in our lives in
order to explore the theme of our lives?
play our cards right and give ourselves
permission to be our best self. Thanks
Bashar.
>> All 52 are symbolic of the template
level because it can be mixed and
matched in any number of ways. It's not
any one card. It's all of them that
represents and symbolizes the template
level which is created by the choices
you make in spirit to have a physical
experience. So as above so below. You
use the energy of the consciousness
field to arrange
certain kinds of blueprints that will
manifest physiologically as the theme
you will explore in physical reality.
And the idea of any kind of permission
slip like a normal deck of cards or
tarot cards or any kind of divination
system represents to some degree the
idea of the template level. Now you have
some freedom in that with your free will
as to how you experience the template
you laid out for yourself. And sometimes
some things can be altered or shifted.
But in general, the choices made by you
as a spirit will be played out as the
cards you are dealt. But you can shift
them around a little bit here and there
with your free will. But you will play
that game. That's what you decided as a
spirit. So that's how the cards
represent the idea of the template level
in energy that then becomes crystallized
down in frequency down into what you
experience as the physical card game
that you are playing. Playing the right
cards, as you say, is easy when you
simply follow the formula. That's the
secret to playing your best hand.
>> Hey, how are you, Bashar?
>> Perfect. And you?
>> Yeah, I'm fine. Uh let's see. My
questions are
um are feelings or thoughts the higher
priority for manifesting our reality?
Because it seems like
uh unresolved feelings manifest over our
thoughts. So how are they linked? And
>> this is how it works. First you begin
with beliefs and definitions. What you
believe to be true is reinforced by the
idea of feeling that it is true,
thinking that it is true, and behaving
as if it is true. Belief systems use
feelings, emotions, thoughts, and
behaviors to reinforce the validity and
the reality of the belief system because
physical reality isn't really real.
Therefore, beliefs have to make you
believe that it is real. And they do so
by reinforcing what you believe to be
true with the idea that it feels true.
You think it's true and you behave as if
it's true. That's the priority. That's
the order in which it happens. You
cannot have a behavior. You cannot have
a thought and you cannot have an emotion
without first believing or defining that
something is true for you. Beliefs are
the blueprint that allow you to build
the house of your physical reality. So
it all starts with that. So when you
behave a certain way, when you think
certain thoughts, when you feel certain
emotions, they all go back to what must
I believe to be true about myself in
order to feel, think, and behave this
way. Does that help you?
>> Yeah. So if I want to change the belief
system, uh the action or how I behave
would be the best way to start and then
the feelings and thoughts.
>> You can start from any direction you
wish. But in a sense, the most efficient
way to change a belief system is to
figure out what that belief is telling
you.
>> Figure out why you're buying into it.
>> Because it may simply be a habit that
you have because you've been taught to
believe this way. It may be that you're
getting something out of believing that
way because you don't hold on to any
belief you don't think serves you. So
even if it doesn't seem to serve you,
you may have a belief that says that the
alternative would be worse than holding
on to the beliefs you have, even if
they're not comfortable because you all
want to believe that everything needs to
serve you, which is true. It can. But
sometimes you have beliefs and you hold
on to them even if you know they're not
the best beliefs to hold on to because
you have a belief that the alternative
would be worse. And therefore, you'll
still hold on to whatever it is you're
holding on to until you change until you
understand that the idea that something
worse will happen if you behave more
like your true self is a fallacy. So you
have to examine why the belief is there
to begin with. Allow yourself to
understand why you're buying into it and
be honest in your self-investigation of
what you believe will happen if you
actually go in a direction you say you
would prefer to. Once you understand
that a negative and fear-based belief is
simply telling you a story that isn't
necessarily true, then you can see that
it is nonsensical and illogical. And as
soon as it is nonsensical, you will drop
it because you don't hold on to things
that don't make sense. If you do hold on
to things that don't make sense, it's
because you have a belief that says it
makes more sense than the alternative.
>> This is what we call the motivational
mechanism in your psychology as humans.
You always always without fail
move in the direction of what you
believe serves you. You always without
fail move away from what you believe
does not serve you. So if you see
yourself choosing things that you know
intellectually don't serve you, it can
only mean you've defined it and attached
a belief to it that says it's better
than the alternative. It serves you
better than the alternative. Find out
why you believe that and when you expose
the belief and the story it's telling
you, you will see that it makes no sense
and it will be dropped. It will be gone.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Yes.
Uh um
let's see uh the next question is uh
from the soul's perspective
um is the physical body like a
radiocontrolled car where you uh the
soul uh puts inputs to make it go left
and right and then there's always input
also input from the environment. So it's
like uh
>> to some degree you can use whatever
analogy you wish
but the idea really is that the physical
world and the physical body is a
projection of the soul's consciousness.
It's like putting on a diving suit more
than the idea of a remote control car.
It's like putting on a diving suit or a
diving mask and going diving under the
ocean. The mask helps you see underneath
the ocean clearly.
It's not designed to tell you what to
do. It's designed to tell you what
you're experiencing more clearly. When
you leave the physical reality, it's
like taking off the diving mask and
going back to the surface.
So, even though you have free will as a
physical being, the soul determines what
the general trajectory is from its own
free will. And that may be what the
physical mind thinks of as destiny. In
other words, you are the person you are.
You will do everything as the person you
are. You cannot actually fundamentally
change the person that you are. Although
the personality can shift to a great
degree, but it's still happening to you
as you think of yourself as a separate
autonomous being. So you have the free
will to experience the destiny of the
soul in any way, shape or form that the
physical mind chooses to. positive,
negative, happy, sad, whatever, fast,
slow, up, down, but you will walk that
path because it was determined by your
free will as a soul. Is this helping?
>> Yeah. Yeah. The diving suit uh was a
much better uh metaphor than the radio
control car.
>> All right.
>> Thank you.
>> Um two more questions really fast. Uh
>> yes. who um when uh when a soul wants to
have an experience here on earth and
many souls wants to have an experience
here on earth uh who gets gets priority.
>> There is no need for priority because
there are a multitude of infinite
parallel realities that can have a
similar experience.
>> Uhhuh.
Okay. And then the last question, uh, on
your planet, uh, do you fart and do you
laugh at your own farts like humans do?
[laughter]
>> We laugh, but we don't eat, so we don't
fart.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Uh, I think that was
all. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Ao.
>> Ao,
good day, Bashar. I would like to know
about the Bosnian pyramids, the ones
located in Visoko.
Uh, and like who built them and for what
purpose? And um, yeah, anything you can
tell me about
the pyramids
in Visoko in Bosnia.
Thank you.
pyramids around your planet at a certain
time were all built relatively close to
one another in time around your 10,500
years ago.
The idea is that they were energy
collectors to balance the earth that had
gone through a catastrophic change when
it was impacted by a cometary body that
caused the annihilation of your
Atlantean civilization.
And therefore knowledge and energy was
preserved in many pyramids around the
planet and also they were used as an
energy balancing system to bring the
planet back into alignment so it could
recuperate and heal. There are other
things that they were used for but we
will not go into that right now.
>> Hello Basha
>> and to you. Good day.
>> I'm very excited to be here. Thank you
for for talking to me.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure. What
would you like to discuss? Um, so I've
been I've been following my excitement
more and more since I kind of started to
listen to to you speak and I've it feels
really great and I I've been doing some
like bigger and some smaller changes and
I'm I'm following your advice of this
thing of basically following my
excitement more moment to moment because
there's no like one big thing in that
sense.
>> All right. Now do remember the entire
formula not just follow your excitement.
There's other pieces to it. Yes. Yes.
Yes, I know.
>> All right.
>> Um and I um I think what I'm like one
thing that just as an as an example that
I I was I quit one one job that I I felt
like I was not excited about at all.
>> Um and now I have more free time which
is fun. Um, and then sometimes I
>> I I get kind of frustrated with myself
because I I feel like I sit there and I
have I know that I have all these
options to to act on, but I don't I kind
of don't know what to do. And I wonder,
>> yes, you do. Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
Yes, you do. The idea again isn't that
complicated. Don't over complicate it.
If you have different options, decide
for yourself which one is not only more
attractive, more exciting than any other
option, but which one can you act on,
which one can you do something about. If
it seems that more than one is equal,
you might as well flip a coin. Remember,
synchronicity comes to bear in this
because if you flip a coin and say, "All
right, heads option A, tails option B."
And you flip the coin, one of two things
might happen. Let's say it lands on
tails, option B, and you find yourself
going, "Oh, goody." Or you find yourself
going, "Oh, I wish it had been option A
instead. Oh, I wish it had been option
A." Then you will know that that was the
one that was more exciting. or if you do
head down a path that isn't necessarily
the most exciting path for you at that
moment, synchronicity will create
certain circumstances that will turn you
around in the correct direction. That's
how it works. It's an automatic
mechanism. So, you don't have to sit
there and wonder and wonder and be
frustrated. Just act on whatever you are
capable of acting on that contains more
excitement than anything else as far as
you can determine. And let synchronicity
guide you with the red light green light
aspect of its being of its nature which
means it will bring you opportunities
you can act on and take further green
light synchronicity. It will prevent you
from acting on certain things that are
not the correct path for you right now.
Red light synchronicity just like you
follow your traffic lights when you
drive. You understand?
>> So the starting and stopping
>> is the way synchronicity guides you. No,
not right now. Don't act in that
direction. Act in this direction.
Whatever you can act on. And you have to
use your imagination. Be very creative
about the idea of what it means to take
action on something in every way that
you possibly can that has to do with
that thing you say excites you. Even if
you have to simulate the reality, that's
taking an action on it.
Let me give you an example that many
people on your planet have used. There
are many people who you call celebrities
that are famous, but you will hear
stories from many of them that before
they were actually able to literally do
what it is that they now do that they're
famous for, they acted it out. They
simulated it. Even sometimes going so
far for someone who might be a public
speaker in an auditorium or a game show
host or a late night interviewer as to
go into a space, set it up like it's
really happening. Even to the level of
putting fake people in the audience,
maybe even just cardboard cutouts, and
doing their routine as if it's really
happening. Because then you're training
your body to get used to the vibration
of the reality of that. And that will
make you attract it more strongly by
doing anything you can to simulate
anything you can to take an action in
the direction of what excites you more
than any other choice. And when we talk
about that, it can also be very simple
things. We don't mean when we say follow
your passion, follow your excitement
that it has to be a grand project or
come with trumpets or be a lifespanning
career. Tada! Here's your passion. No.
Every day you have little options,
simple options. I can take a walk. I can
read a book. I can have lunch with a
friend. I can watch a movie.
Just choose the one that has more
attractiveness, more curiosity, more
excitement, even just the tiniest bit
more that you're able to act on than any
other one. And just do that first.
You're still following your excitement
by doing it on that level. And
eventually, it will usually snowball
through synchronicity to bring you more
and more opportunities to act on your
passion in bigger and bigger and bigger
ways. But the point is, it doesn't
really matter if it does or not because
you're still following your excitement
just by making sure that every day the
options you choose are more exciting
than any other option and taking action
on the ones that you can. That's all
there is to it. You don't have to make
it a big mystery or over complicate it
or overthink it. That's why you're
frustrated.
>> So, you're saying I'm frustrated because
I am making it way more complicated.
>> Yes.
Because I feel like sometimes it's it's
literally that I have like an afternoon
off and I'm sitting at home and I I I I
don't know like I'm I I
>> Then you're not using your creative
imagination
>> sitting at home. Why are you speaking
with us today? Was this more exciting
than any other option?
>> Yes.
>> Well, you see that wasn't hard. So, what
will you do after this conversation is
over? What are your options after this
conversation is over? What are your
options? Name some.
>> Um, probably go to sleep because it's
quite late here.
>> All right. Going to sleep can be
exciting. That's fine. But let's say
it's morning. What would be some of your
options?
>> Um, I usually like go for a walk, go to
workout. Um,
>> do you enjoy those things? Are they
expressions of your passion?
>> Uh, yes, they are.
>> Are you sure? Because you kind of
hesitated.
[laughter]
No, I'm sure.
>> All right. Because remember, sometimes
you may be sort of doing what excites
you, but you may not be doing it in the
most exciting way because the idea of
following your passion requires every
component of it to also be the most
exciting way. So you can do a thing but
where you're doing it, how you're doing
it, when you're doing it, with whom
you're doing it all have to be of that
vibration or you're not really following
your passion. So you get to decide the
way in which you're actually acting on
your excitement. And isn't that an
exciting thought?
>> It is actually.
>> All right. So, just make sure that
whatever it is you choose to do out of
the options that you have, whether it's
taking a walk or working out, you're
doing it in the most exciting way as a
whole system. All the components of it
are being done in the most exciting way.
And if you can't find that one of the
components is the most exciting way you
would prefer to do it, invent, use your
creative imagination to create your
exciting way of doing it.
>> Yes.
Yeah, I think that that what you just
said with the creative Yeah, that that
actually helps a lot. I've never thought
about it that way that I have the power
to do that.
>> You do.
>> You do. So,
>> if that makes things more exciting, then
you're on the right path.
>> Yeah.
>> Does this help?
>> Thank you. Yeah, that that helped a lot.
Yes, it really did.
>> All right. Does that serve you today?
>> Yes. Then [clears throat] we thank you
for your interaction. AO,
>> thank you. Have a great day.
>> Of course. Always. You, too. [laughter]
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> Why would I have anything else?
>> Sorry.
>> Why would I choose anything else?
>> Oh, yeah. That's um makes sense.
>> Yes, [laughter] I know. That's why I
said it.
>> So, go see
>> and don't choose what doesn't make
sense.
>> I will. Thank you so much, Rashar.
>> It's up to you. Thank [laughter] you.
to say good day to you this day of your
time. How are you all? Uh
[cheering]
>> all right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you. Once again, we thank each and every
one of you individually and all of you
together collectively for the
co-creation of this interaction and the
opportunity for this transmission. At
this time,
we will begin this transmission by
reminding each and every one of you that
it is titled masks.
We will be doing this
part of the transmission in the
beginning a little bit differently than
we've ever done before.
It will be a little unusual but it will
be for the purpose of more clearly
illustrating the concept that we will be
sharing with you today.
So
Nania,
>> yes,
>> you have something that you can bring
up.
>> I do.
>> All right.
>> Okay.
>> [snorts]
>> Now
I would suggest
for the greatest impact
that all of you close your eyes
and I will tell you when to open them.
So eyes closed.
[groaning]
You may open them.
>> Now, we understand that for some of you,
your first reaction may be that's
creepy.
[laughter]
And that's all right
because the idea of the masks
is to understand something very
important about the relationship between
your higher mind and your physical mind.
And that is that what you consider
yourself to be as a person.
When you look in the mirror, what you're
seeing is a mask. You are projecting,
you are channeling the idea of a portion
of your consciousness into the
experience of physical reality. You are
always channeling. Therefore, every
single moment. And your physical face is
a projection. It's a mask. It's a
representation. It's a symbol
of the idea
that you call a physical experience.
It's how you have focused your
consciousness in such a way in a
space-time linear framework to
experience this idea you call physical
reality. But we remind you that in a
sense is artificial construct, a
projection of consciousness.
Therefore, from the higher mind's point
of view,
your physical face, your physical
personality
is truly just a mask. It's not really
all that you are, but a very small
portion of it and a temporary portion of
it for the purpose of navigating in your
physical reality.
Therefore, the idea of this particular
permission slip
is to begin
when you have the excitement to do so to
go out find a mask
that covers a majority of your face
similar to what you are seeing now.
It can be any kind of a mask you wish it
to be. We would suggest, however, that
it be relatively plain because the idea
of this is to form a neutralization of
what you typically see when you look in
a mirror. So that you can really begin
to start to relate to your face through
this exercise as a projection, as a
mask, and not associate it with the idea
of your personality in the way you think
of yourselves typically on a day-to-day
basis as a person.
When you begin to neutralize the idea
this way, you will begin to form a
dissociation
with your physical face a little bit in
this exercise.
And if at first it feels a little bit
creepy, that's all right because the
first phase for some people will be to
get in touch with the idea of whatever
negative or fear-based beliefs may come
up in doing this. Because we understand
that many times on your planet when
people dawn masks
in your culture, for a variety of
reasons, many people will assume that
there's a nefarious reason for doing so.
that you're hiding something that you
don't want people to see. So, some of
that may come up at first, and that's
all right. Just let it do so.
Eventually, you will begin, as you stare
in the mirror at the mask instead of
your face, you will begin to relax and
neutralize the idea of any negative
connotations or associations.
And you'll begin to dissociate from the
idea of your face and begin to
understand your personality as a mask,
as a projection that the higher mind
sees it as such. And you can begin then
by creating that dissociation,
by creating a disfamiliarity,
you can begin to see through the eyes of
the mask more like the inner being, the
higher being that you also actually are.
Once you lose touch by doing this a few
times, practicing it a few times, lose
touch with the idea of what you're used
to looking at in terms of the emotional
expressions, the physical marks,
the frame of your face. All of that you
will begin to see through different
eyes.
You will begin to in a sense feel like
you're pulling back, dissociating,
disconnecting, uncoupling from physical
reality a little bit and a little bit
more each time.
Now, please understand this is not about
glossing anything over. It's not about
denying your humanity. It's not about
denying anything negative or fear-based
beliefs that may come up. It's about
truly acknowledging that they are there,
but then allowing that to be part of
you. and then allowing yourself to
neutralize and relax about it and start
to feel a little bit of this
disconnection from physical reality from
the typical expressions you have from
the typical way you have of
communicating with people even without
words through minor facial expressions
attitudes emotionality.
This may take some getting used to but
that's all right. You will eventually if
you do it often enough if you practice
and eventually you'll begin to start
seeing things a bit differently from
another perspective. You'll start
associating the idea of looking through
the eyes of the mask with looking
through your physical eyes as if it is a
mask. And the more you can do this, the
more you can start to form a basis, a
foundation for starting to see things
more in the way that your higher mind
does. Because your higher mind does
relate to your physical persona as a
mask. And the more you do that, your
thoughts will be different. Your
perspective will be different. How you
interact with physical reality will be
different. You will start to blend and
balance the idea of your physical mind
and the higher mind in such a way that
you can move through life as a more
complete person.
And then even when you take the mask
off, you will remember that your face is
still a mask, is still not everything
that you are. Again, not to discount the
beauty of it. But you will find yourself
more blended, more balanced, being in
the world but not of the world. And that
knowing that the world is in you
more and more each time you do this. And
when you finally allow yourself more
opportunity to function closer to the
frequency of the higher mind,
then different inspirations, different
thoughts, different ideas will come to
you than may have been able to come to
you when you associated more strongly
with the idea of your physical face,
your physical personality.
You'll begin to truly begin to see
things that hereto for were invisible to
you. begin to see a broader picture, a
bigger perspective from a higher
position. You'll begin to understand how
synchronicity works by seeing through
the eyes of the higher mind, through the
eyes of the mask of your physical
personality.
This is a very, very fun permission
slip, but also one that takes a little
getting used to. You can feel a little
disoriented at first when doing this,
but that's all right. The more you
practice, the more you'll get it, the
more you'll feel the balancing act, and
the more inspirations will come to you.
And you may even grow to use this
technique
as a way of getting in touch with higher
plains of existence,
with other spirit realms, other
consciousness levels, other beings, and
other dimensions. It can go that far.
Again, you can keep your feet on the
ground and yet form this creative and
constructive positive dissociation with
your personality, with the physical
plane, with the physical experience in a
balanced way. And this will give you not
only greater outer sight, but greater
inner sight as well.
How do you think we look?
Oh, thank you.
And so
this is of course not exact, but you
understand it is somewhat a
representation of how we actually look
as a hybrid being.
Our skin color is about this white.
Our eyes, while similar to yours, have
enlarged pupils that are this black. But
you would see a little bit of the iris
around it. More like what you are used
to seeing as an eye.
But the interesting thing here also in
this exercise in this endeavor in this
presentation
is that you're also getting an
opportunity a little bit to experience
the idea of communicating with us
physically.
And so even though this is not entirely
representative of how we really look, it
is a close approximation of a symbol
that allows us to come a little closer
and allows you to come a little closer
by remembering this experience and how
this mask looks right now to open
contact to physical contact with us one
day. Remember that there is only a small
percentage of our energy coming through
the channel. Never more at this
particular moment than 10% although 15
is possible.
But on the day when there is physical
contact, there will be stages to this
that will allow you to be approached in
stages in steps at whatever rate at
whatever pace you are comfortable and
allow you more opportunity to
[clears throat] integrate within
yourself all those energies and all
those beliefs that will allow you to
take a step closer to us and a step
closer to actual physical contact. So
this is a very very early simulation
of that experience
and therefore take advantage of this by
taking a moment to really look at the
mask on the channel's face and
understand
and again of course you never have to
believe this. We are not forcing this.
But if you're open to it, take this
opportunity to understand.
You are communicating with an
extraterrestrial being right now.
And by this mask, seeing a slightly
closer representation of how it would
appear in your physical reality.
So take a moment to absorb this, to let
it in. Let the feelings, the energies,
the vibrational states run through you.
Taste them, savor them, explore them,
and let your imagine fill in the rest.
And imagine that we are in fact sitting
right in front of you physically having
this conversation
in what you would consider to be a
normal fashion. a normal everyday thing
that you can interact with us in this
way
in your reality that is no longer the
reality you used to be in but a new
reality, a link, a bridge, a third
reality different than mine, different
than yours. A meeting place
in which we can exchange
more deeply,
more concretely
and which will give you more
opportunities to see the probabilities
that can issue from such meetings and
the paths that open up to you that lead
to the stars. So we thank you for this
opportunity of allowing us to present
this symbol
to you to give you an opportunity to
understand how to come a little bit
closer to us
without freaking out.
Does this help you? So find a mask, do
the exercise if you wish every day if
you wish. See what happens bit by bit.
Take your time. No rush. No hurry. When
you feel a little disoriented, that's
all right. Slow down. Take a breath. You
will start to feel the dissociation in
time. Keep it balanced
and allow yourself to let it be all
right
to let yourself see through the eyes of
the higher mind. Knowing that this
physical face is your mask is your
diving mask that allows you to see more
clearly in physical reality and yet can
open up new vistas to you by blending
the physical eyes and the higher mind
senses
to create a new experience
in a new world and a new reality for
you. So, we thank you,
>> Nania.
>> Yes.
>> Would you like to take back the mask?
>> Okay.
>> It's a test of your own sense of
selfworth.
>> Um, and this person is asking, "How do I
connect with my oversoul? And how do I
know that I've been connected with my
oversoul? And how can I ask my oversoul
questions?"
There is no way you can be disconnected
from your over soul because you're an
extension of it.
So you know you are connected if you
simply understand how things work.
Everything is one thing. Even if you
create what appears to be a
differentiation, an extension, a
so-called separation. The word
separation is only a separation of
experience of perspective. It's not
literally a mechanical separation.
There's no such thing. You can't be
separated from existence and the
oversoul is part of existence and so are
you. So you are connected by the
description and definition of how
existence is structured, how it works,
how it exists.
How you can feel like there's
communication coming through again is
follow the formula and trust that the
synchronicities that pop up in your life
that you become more aware of are not
only coming from the oversoul but from
the soul from the higher mind from
spirit guides. But there is really no
need to absolutely differentiate where
it's coming from. In some senses that
can actually get in your way and prevent
you from simply receiving the guidance
no matter where it's coming from. So
it's not that important to always know
where it's coming from and if it is
important then something in the
synchronicity will show you where it's
coming from.
>> Okay. And um do we exist independently
when we pass or do we get absorbed into
the oversoul?
>> Everything exists simultaneously.
And the idea is that if you allow your
consciousness to rise to the level of
the oversoul, you will experience
yourself as the oversoul. Absorption
doesn't mean you lose anything. It means
you still retain the unique identity
that you are and therefore experience
things from that level. In the same way
that as you became an adult, you didn't
lose the experiences you experienced
when you were a child. You don't
necessarily consider yourself a child
anymore. But it's not like the child
experiences have disappeared, have gone
away. You can still relate to them. You
can still call upon them if you need to.
You can still talk about them. It's just
that you're not coming from that level
anymore. So the child experiences while
on one hand you could say have been
absorbed into your adulthood, it's not
like the child is gone. It's still
there. It's still a part of you. It
still exists on its own right. And you
can tap into it and you can call upon
it. But the idea is that you're simply
now coming from the adult level in the
same way that you would now come from
the oversoul level without losing the
individual personality because now
that's part of the oversoul and it can
call on it or refer to it or tap into it
anytime it wishes. It's just that for
the most part you're now coming from the
higher level as you
>> and um recently this person has been
reading the law of one by Ra and to
their understanding they reference the
dimensional progressions that happen
from second to eighth densities of
vibration.
How, if at all, does this reflect what
you are speaking of in terms of the
oversoul? Are they mirrored concepts,
divergent ones, or something else?
>> It's just another way of expressing the
same ideas. There are different levels
of consciousness that exist on different
density levels, different frequency
levels, which is the same thing as
saying density. And therefore it's just
another way of expressing a certain
limited hierarchical way of looking at
what is relevant for your particular
reality. As we have said in a past
transmission, the nine levels of
consciousness is sort of similar to the
idea of what the law of one is talking
about when it talks about eight
different density levels. So the idea is
simply another way to frame that there
are different frequencies that represent
different levels of awareness, different
experiences and expressions of
consciousness. It's just another way of
saying the same basic thing, but maybe
with a little bit of emphasis on a
certain direction because of perhaps the
way the information needed to be
delivered by that entity to the people
that were listening to that entity or
the way a question was asked may require
a slight differentiation in the way the
information is delivered but
fundamentally it's the same concept.
>> Okay.
Uh, this person was diagnosed with ALS
and wonders when they die, will the
formula still apply or is it just for
humans on Earth?
>> Aspects of the idea of the formula will
still apply because you can still follow
your passion even when you're a spirit.
And in fact, in a sense, it becomes more
self-evident that that's your nature to
do so. So aspects of it will still apply
and you will understand that it applies
in the way that is now relevant for you
as a spirit. You don't necessarily have
to do all of the formula in the same way
you did it as a physical experiential
being. But you will do your version of
it as a spirit because it's not like you
have to dig into belief systems anymore
in the same way. All your belief systems
are transparent and immediately apparent
and relevant to you, but in a different
kind of form of awareness. It's more
about simply knowing yourself, knowing
what is relevant for you. It's not that
you have to dip into a subconscious or
an unconscious to reveal belief systems
anymore as a spirit because everything
is right there in front of your face, so
to speak.
So some aspects of the formula will be
relevant for spirit and some aspects are
only relevant for your physical reality
experience.
Um and where do innovative ideas come
from?
>> All that is but they filter down in
different ways through different
translations into the different levels
of consciousness of oversoul and soul
and higher mind and so forth. As we have
said, it's more about the idea as far as
the physical perspective is concerned
that the higher mind conceives. So you
could say that is the inspiration. After
all, inspiration
is referring to spirit, non-physical
reality.
So it is everywhere at once, but it
filters through, it translates through
the higher mind. Then the physical brain
is the receiver and then the physical
mind is the perceiver. Now that doesn't
mean that the physical mind doesn't have
its ability to receive it and act upon
it creatively. It can certainly take
what it receives and perceives in many
creative directions. But the idea is
that the physical mind is therefore,
shall we say, manipulating and making
malleable what it is that has been
conceived by the higher mind and
received by the brain. And it then is
allowed by the physical mind to be
perceived in whatever way the physical
mind feels is its creative ability to
arrange it in a way that works for
what's relevant for the physical mind.
So creativity exists on every level and
in some sense inspiration exists on
every level. But the overall very large
generalized idea is that inspiration
comes from the higher level down through
to the physical level which still has
the ability to be inspired to be
creative in how it represents and how it
expresses and how it acts upon what it
has received from the higher mind.
>> Okay. Um you said in a recent
transmission that all death is suicide
because mostly we have already
determined the window of our lifesp time
from spirit.
>> Yes.
>> Does this mean that people who commit
suicide would have died anyway around
the same time or from some other cause
if they had made that particular choice?
Or are the lifespans that are chosen in
spirit actually cut short if someone
chooses to commit suicide?
It depends upon the person. It depends
upon the theme and it depends upon the
methodology in terms of the belief
systems and energy states that surround
what you perceive to be suicide. So
there can be exceptions. In general, the
way most suicides occur in your
collective society is a cutting short of
an agreement. Therefore, the individual
once in spirit may realize that and may
wish to continue the theme in some way,
shape or form, whether physically or
non-physically to complete the theme, to
complete the agreement, because it may
have been made from the misunderstanding
or lack of understanding that they had
more choices than they thought they had
to continue the life and finish out the
agreements that they chose to begin
with. So by cutting themselves short
they may continue in some way shape or
form. But nevertheless the idea of
simply saying all death is suicide is a
generalized recognition that in general
by letting it happen naturally by
letting it unfold naturally you do
generally allow a window of timing to
occur. But it can be very specific or it
can be very random so to speak. So just
as there have been individuals in your
society that have said
I'm going to die precisely at 10:27 on
Tuesday morning and then they do
obviously they simply became aware of
the fact that they had for some reason
chosen to have a very specific range of
time for their lifespan. Others may say,
well, I'll choose to go out by some
particular quick or slow methodology
when it generally suits the idea that I
have completed my theme, but there's no
hurry to it. So maybe they will be taken
out by what you typically call an
accident or a disease or something along
that line. Others may simply say, you
know, I'll have the general idea of
having a randomly chosen death. It's
like an analogy of your roulette wheel
where they will allow the wheel to spin
and they will allow the ball to go
around and around and around. And there
may be any number of ways that they
could allow themselves to pass into
spirit, but they will accept wherever
the ball falls randomly by all the
opportunities that spin past until it
slows down and the ball finds its niche.
And they will simply accept that as the
proper timing for their depth. However,
in this lifetime, there is also a way to
change your theme. Once one theme is
finished and you may extend the lifespan
sometimes to be able to afford the
opportunity to explore a different
theme. Those kinds of choices are now
available. But they are also most likely
made to begin with in spirit saying,
"All right, well, when I'm done with one
theme, I'll hang around and see if I can
receive another theme to explore and
sort of get a two for one in a physical
lifetime." There are any number of these
kinds of choices that can be made from
the spirit and even from the idea of the
physical personality if it recognizes
consciously that it is aware of what
theme it has been exploring and is aware
that there may be some benefit to
exploring a different theme.